[indistinct chatter and laughter]
[birds squawking]
[boy exhaling]
[theme music playing]
[Gon and Killua]
Ready? Go!
[both chomping]
Kurapika!
-I'm happy for you.
-Huh?
The Spiders are dead.
And that means that you can finally focus
on your main goal, right?
You have to go out there and find them.
The eyes of your people.
Gon...
And if there's anything we can do
to help you out, just--
[snickering]
-[Gon] Why, you!
-[Killua yelping]
You did it first.
I was just getting revenge!
[Gon] I didn't do it on purpose!
-[Killua] You did so, you big liar.
-[chuckles]
[both grunting]
[chuckles]
What are you so upset about, huh?
We sold one piece and walked away
with a cool 355 million Jenny!
That's the problem.
It could have sold for a lot more.
[Leorio] We got plenty!
Wrong. We could have gotten
well over 400 million for it,
if we'd just waited.
Bad luck, that's what it is.
You sure take this seriously.
Besides, even if we did get more,
it’s not like you would’ve seen any of it.
[Zepile] That's not the issue here.
If we take the money and run,
that’s 170 million apiece! [cackling]
Are you really friends
with Gon and Killua?
-[phone ringing]
-I'm kidding, lighten up.
Yeah, hello?
Oh. Hey, Kurapika!
Wow, it's been a while
since we were all together!
Yeah.
[Gon] Where's Mr. Zepile?
[Leorio] Oh, he went back over
to pick up the check
and find some more loot to sell.
Hey, you know something?
[Kurapika] What?
You've got this intensity about you.
Your presence is a whole lot stronger
than it was.
Really?
Well, I wish I could say the same for you.
And you’ve also gotten
a lot more annoying!
[elevator dings]
[Leorio] Oh, yeah.
I heard you killed a Troupe member.
How the hell did you do that
when you only learned Nen recently?
If the reason you’re asking
is that you’re planning
to catch the Spiders yourself,
you can stop.
That's not the only reason.
You've mastered Nen and we want
to learn how too.
Not just to catch the Spiders,
but because we'll need it in the future.
You don't want my advice.
I'm afraid it won't do you
any good, anyway.
Because my power can only be used
against the Troupe.
[all gasp]
[Gon] A contract with conditions?
Yes.
Your mental state has
an incredibly powerful effect on your Nen.
The more determined you are,
the more powerful the Nen.
But the risk incurred is great, as well.
In exchange for stronger Nen,
I vowed that I would only use it
against the Spiders.
And I established a rule for myself.
Oh, yeah? What kind of rule is it?
My chains must be used
exclusively on the Spiders.
Or I will die as a result.
[both gasp]
Hold on! What do you mean?
There is a Nen dagger in my heart.
If I break the rule, the blade
will pierce through, killing me.
The rule proves my resolve.
That's the contract with conditions.
My ability is the product of my pure
and unadulterated hatred.
It will only work when used
on the Spiders.
I'm telling you this because I trust you.
Don't tell anyone else.
What the hell?
Why would you tell us something
that's so damn important?
Huh?
I'm not really sure.
Maybe I felt dispirited
because their leader is dead now.
It'll be fine if we keep it quiet.
No it won't.
One of the surviving members
has the power to read memories.
If the Spiders find out about this,
Kurapika's a dead man!
But she didn't learn anything last time.
You're right, but that's only
because we didn't know
Kurapika was the chain user back then.
Okay, so that means we just have
to stay away from them.
Since they've already checked you out,
they think that you're clean.
[Killua]
There's also a guy called Nobunaga.
He's really dangerous.
He's looking for Kurapika
and he's still trying to get me and Gon.
[Leorio] But he doesn’t know
that you guys know Kurapika… does he?
-No.
-Well, then what's the problem?
Just keep your distance
from the memory reader.
You and everyone else
who knows Kurapika’s the chain user.
I've also been in contact with Hisoka.
[Leorio grunts]
With Hisoka?
[Kurapika] He knows that I am
the chain user, as well.
We had made a pact, but his target,
the leader of the Phantom Troupe,
is dead gone now.
So I have no idea what he'll do.
[thunder rumbling]
Hold on just a second.
What do you mean, we're leaving?
[Chrollo] Just like I told you.
We're leaving tonight.
We'll take the rest of the treasure.
And that's the end of it.
-[thunder rumbling]
-[Nobunaga] Not yet.
[Chrollo] What else is there?
[Nobunaga] We have to find the chain user.
-[Chrollo] You're obsessed.
-[Nobunaga] Damn right, I am.
We haven’t avenged Uvo’s death yet
and you want us to just pack and leave?
He’s gonna be bored in the next world
if we don’t send the chain user
to join him.
Why don't you cut it out, Nobunaga?
The boss gave an order.
Right. The boss’ orders are absolute.
But I’ve got to wonder, are you really
speaking as our leader, Chrollo?
Nobunaga, knock it off!
Shut up! I'm trying to talk
to Chrollo, here.
[Chrollo] Before I can answer...
Nobunaga...
I need you to answer my questions.
[thunder rumbling]
[Chrollo] Nobunaga,
I need you to answer my questions.
-What's your birthday?
-Huh?
[Chrollo] I asked what day you were born.
September 8th, in the year '70.
[Chrollo] Blood type?
[Nobunaga] B positive.
[Chrollo] Name?
Nobunaga Hazama. You know that!
What is this?
What do you wanna know next, huh?
Nothing. That's enough.
Write it all down. Here.
Write it down?
You could’ve said that to begin with.
Huh? The hell is this?
Your fortune in verse.
One hundred percent accurate.
I can tell the future, a skill I stole
from Nostrade's daughter.
And you're sure
that it's completely accurate?
[Chrollo] Each of the four verses predicts
what's going to happen in that week.
"Forever set, a previous moon is lost.
The others mourn him with ceremony grand.
The wolf alone misses out
on morning frost,
and seeks frost moon’s shadow
across the land.
Harvest barren, wine spilled,
lovers slumber
beside the bloody Scarlet Eyes.
Though cut in half shall be your number,
unhindered the spider flies."
This is the fortune
Nostrade's daughter gave me yesterday.
It says a precious moon has been lost,
so is that...
It's Uvo.
[gasps lightly]
[Chrollo]
That girl didn't know anything about Uvo.
In fact, she'd never heard of any of us.
Yet she was able to predict our attack
on the Mafia auction.
And there were fans
of her fortune-telling among the Ten Dons.
I get it. That’s why the first time
we attacked,
somebody had already moved
the merchandise to a new location.
Kinda curious.
What was Nobunaga's fortune?
My hand wrote it itself.
I have no idea what it is.
Nobunaga can tell you.
[Shalnark] Well, what's it say?
Come next week,
five of us will most likely die.
Oh, yeah? Does it say which five?
[Nobunaga]
No. I can't figure any of this out.
Well, I kind of understand
the second poem.
The spider losing half its number.
The spider would be us, wouldn't it?
[Nobunaga] Yeah.
And the limbs would be the members,
so half would be six.
That means five more after Uvo.
The very same line appeared
in my fortune too.
[Shizuku] Let me see that.
Hey, Boss. Do you think
you can tell my fortune?
"Forever set, a precious moon is lost.
The others mourn him with ceremony grand.
But lonely not, be the moon of frost.
Soon your blood will join
his grave of sand.
In the chamber of treasure ill-gotten,
there is no choice but endless sleep.
Your greatest fear should solitude be,
lest upon your lonesome form he creep.
Just as I expected.
Looks like I'm gonna die next week.
Seriously?
Yeah, you see?
I only got two poems in mine.
And look, Pakunoda and Shalnark
are gonna die too.
-Oh?
-Really?
How do you know it's Pakunoda
and Shalnark?
It think the months mentioned here
refer to Phantom Troupe members.
The frost moon is November.
Uvo's the 11th member, the 11th month.
[Chrollo] Exactly.
The harvest moon is in September,
the wine moon is August,
and the lover’s moon is June.
This refers to numbers six,
eight and nine.
And "barren" is mentioned,
which I believe implies death.
I’m just not certain
who “Scarlet Eyes” refers to.
Well, it isn't one of us.
I'm guessing it might be a reference
to the chain user.
[gasps]
[Pakunoda] Scarlet Eyes.
I remember now.
The clan whose eyes turned red.
[Feitan] Then there was a survivor?
[Shalnark] So it would seem.
Will he die too?
It's hard to tell.
It doesn’t say anything other
than the guy is bloody.
[Shalnark] Nobunaga, this means
if we fight the chain user,
we'll suffer serious casualties
and lose half our members.
Your ability can be replaced
as easily as mine,
but not Shizuku's or Pakunoda's.
The Troupe can't afford
to lose either of them.
[thunder crashing]
Today is Saturday of the first week.
So if we leave now and return home,
then that means we can avoid
running into the chain user next week.
The best thing about these fortunes
is that if we pay attention...
they tell us how to avoid catastrophe.
If we leave here
without fighting the chain user,
this fortune is 100 percent certain
not to come to pass.
Nobunaga, you and Uvo
were our attack unit.
You were already prepared to die.
I believe that both of you accepted
that role of your own free will.
[Nobunaga] Yeah, that's right.
[Chrollo] Shizuku, Paku and Shal
collect intelligence.
They provide our support.
You could even call them our lifelines.
And your duty is to serve as their shield.
You agree with that assessment?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
[Hisoka] Wait.
You should tell the other members'
fortunes now.
It’s quite possible
that they could provide additional clues
for how to avoid the prophecy.
[Killua] What do we do?
Now that we all know
about Kurapika’s secret,
it’s dangerous to wait.
If Gon or I get captured again,
we won’t be able to escape.
But we do have Kurapika with us now.
So we need to take them out
before they can recover or run.
And we know where their current base is.
If we take too long,
it'll give them a chance to get away.
That means we need to move fast.
They could be making a getaway plan
as we speak.
We don't have time to overthink it.
That woman, the one who reads memories,
is a threat.
But now that their leader’s dead,
I’ll do what Gon suggests
and focus on recovering
my brethren's eyes.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
And you're sure about this?
Look, it's obvious he's made up his mind.
You can try all you want,
there’s no changing it now.
I'm sorry.
But thanks.
I do appreciate the information.
[phone ringing]
It's from Hisoka.
[gasps]
[Hisoka] The corpses were fake.
[Gon] Kurapika?
The corpses were fake.
[Leorio gasps]
You mean the Troupe members?
Yeah. The ones we thought
were dead, aren't!
Of course! A Conjurer could have pulled
that off easily!
Damn it! Why didn't I realize this sooner?
The situation has changed.
Now what?
We're here to help.
Right.
Yeah.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Melody] Kurapika, it's me.
Oh. Melody. What is it?
[Melody] The community has called off
the hunt for the remaining Troupe members.
What?
[Melody] We just received word
that they come from Meteor City.
[Kurapika] The Troupe? Really?
And apparently the order came directly
from the Ten Dons themselves.
They even took the offer for reward money
off the table.
[thunder rumbling]
[Killua] The reward's been rescinded?
Seriously?
So the Phantom Troupe
comes from Meteor City.
It makes sense.
Their identities are still unknown
And the cops haven’t caught them yet.
That would explain all of that.
What is Meteor City?
A place populated by people
who don’t exist,
for all intents and purposes.
There’s a whole city like that?
Yeah. Officially, the town
has a population of zero.
But it’s said that there are at least
ten million people who live there.
It started off as a dump
over 1,500 years ago.
You were allowed to dump anything there.
And whatever trash was thrown away,
that’s what people lived off of.
-Trash, weapons, even people.
-[baby crying]
[Leorio] No matter what’s left there,
the residents take it in
without a second thought.
I’ve heard people from Meteor City
share a bond thinner than water,
but at the same time thicker than blood.
Also, there’s an organization
that provides gold and weapons
under the pretext of dumping garbage.
Namely, the Mafia community.
What? What do you mean?
The Mafia is hunting the Troupe!
In return, the Mafia picks new recruits
from among the residents.
These are people
who basically don't exist, remember?
Perfect for criminal activity.
The Troupe managed to destroy
the intimate business relationship
that used to exist between the Mafia
and Meteor City.
Even after all that's happened,
the Mafia wants to retain the relationship
with Meteor City.
[Hisoka] "With eyes of red,
a customer comes to call.
Half of him an angel, the other death.
Secrets of the moons tell him all.
Those of the frost moon,
he awaits with bated breath.
On the day of the sun,
under this customer’s care,
alone with the man of cross reversed...
Removed from the calendar
is the false hare.
With six months gone, the year is cursed."
What does your fortune say?
Show me.
I don't recommend it.
It might startle you.
Oh, just let me see it.
Very well.
[gasps]
[Pakunoda] Everyone, look at this.
A customer who has eyes of red?
Wait, the secrets of the moons?
Hold on a minute, those would be
our secrets, wouldn’t they?
[Franklin] Hisoka, what is this?
Let me see!
[gasps lightly]
[Nobunaga]
"A red-eyed customer comes into view.
Of bartering and sweet deals he croons.
The sword of law he plunges into you,
and makes off with secrets of the moons.
The 11-legged spider longs for home.
Five more legs shall break
before it's done.
But from your shelter do not roam,
for of those five, you shall be one."
Hisoka.
Did you sell out Uvo?
Answer me!
[narrator]
The words in Hisoka’s fortune changed
the moment it was passed to Pakunoda.
The question is... what could that mean?
[theme music playing]
-[Gon] Coming up, Gon...
-[Killua] And Killua's...
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I'm Gon!
-I'm Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we'll introduce Bonolenov!
He's a Troupe member.
His face, body and powers
are completely covered by bandages.
[both] Spin, spin, spin, spin!
[Gon] Next time:
"Allies and Lies."
-[Killua] My Highness.
-[Gon] Your Highness?
-[Killua] His Highness, Killua!
-[Gon] Yeah, yeah.